Hey there, my friends. It's Tom with
Watchman River. How are you? I hope
you're well. I'm glad you're here.
Sunday by the river. It is raining here
and it's early morning. So, this video
may be a little fuzzy because this
camera is terrible at low lighting
situations, but that's okay cuz I'm a
little fuzzy, too. So, anyway, we're
going to start off in the word of God.
I'm in God's promises for your every
need. It's a little book that contains
scripture. By the way, today is
September 13th. I know that a lot of
people like when I say the dates of the
video. Uh I'm on page 37. Jesus is your
guardian. Let's start off here. I love
this verse. Isaiah 43:2.
When you pass through the waters, I will
be with you. And through the rivers,
they shall not overflow you. When you
walk through the fire, you shall not be
burned, and nor shall the flame scorch
you. Love that verse. Psalm 3:3.
But you, oh Lord, are a shield for me,
my glory, and the one who lifts up my
head.
Deuteronomy 1:30. The Lord your God, who
goes before you, he will fight for you
according to all he did for you in Egypt
before your eyes.
2 Thessalonians 3:3,
"But the Lord is faithful, who will
establish you and guard you from the
evil one."
Exodus 23:22,
"But if you indeed obey his voice and do
all that I speak, then I will be an
enemy to your enemies and an adversary
to your adversaries."
1st Samuel 2:9,
"He will guard the feet of his saints,
but the wicked shall be silent in
darkness, for by strength no man shall
prevail."
Psalm 61:3, "For you have been a shelter
for me, a strong tower from the enemy."
I love this one. Zephaniah 3:17,
"The Lord your God in your midst, the
mighty one, will save. He will rejoice
over you with gladness. He will quiet
you with his love. He will rejoice over
you with singing." Oh, give me an amen.
Thank you. Can you imagine the most high
God singing over you? I just can't even
imagine. It's so beautiful.
Let's do a couple more.
Psalm 91
verse 7. A thousand may fall at your
side and 10,000 at your right hand, but
it shall not come near you.
And Isaiah 59:1 19.
So shall they fear the name of the Lord
from the west and his glory from the
rising of the sun. When the enemy comes
in like a flood, the spirit of the Lord
will lift up a standard against him. Oh,
we serve a powerful God. Powerful,
wonderful most high God. How are you
guys today? I hope you are well. Uh,
Sundays, most of you know, are different
videos from the rest of the week. We
don't cover the news or clown world or
anything. We just do a short video and
use the comment section below so that we
can pray for each other. And we've been
doing this a long time and we're going
to do it till the first Sunday that we
are not here. And I always believe that
every Sunday I'm always like, could this
be the last one? And it could be. You
never know. God knows. The most high God
knows, but we don't. But anyway, that's
what we do here. There are so many
testimonies that have come from the
prayers you guys have said for each
other. And it's just a beautiful thing
and really blessed that we have this
opportunity every Sunday to pray for
each other. Right. just beautiful. And
uh I always ask when you put your
comment and your prayer request, don't
just leave. Maybe look at a few other
comments and pray for them and either
thumb up their comment or reply to them
and let them know you prayed for them
because that is a wonderful feeling when
you put a prayer request. Then you know
that somebody out there somewhere in
this world is praying for you. I mean,
man, that is just what a privilege and a
blessing, right? But anyway, I will say
a prayer if you don't mind and then we
will get busy. And yes, my shoes are
squeaking because they're wet because
it's raining out. Here we go.
Father in heaven,
we thank you. We praise you for you are
good. There is no one like you.
You are righteousness and truth, full of
grace and mercy.
You are the most high God.
I just sit in awe before you because you
are good and you always have a perfect
plan. No matter what our path is, you
always have this perfect plan. We may
not see it, Lord, but in the end, we
always see that you had your hand in it.
And
praise you forever for the way you are.
I lift up the Watching River family to
you, Lord.
In these last days, there are so many
that are struggling financially,
but you are the one who prospers. Lord,
I lift them up to you. Some have health
issues, Lord, and you are the great
physician,
Lord. Touch them today.
When you were here, Jesus, you healed
everyone. Everyone in your path. Lord,
I'm going to ask that you
heal today my brothers and sisters who
need healing.
There are people with spiritual issues
and relationship issues, but you are
again the healer.
I put them in your hands. Lord, I pray
for the people around the world, this
world. They don't know it, Lord, but
they are aching for you.
There is such uncertainty in this world.
They are aching for you, Jesus.
Please do a mighty work today.
There will be so many prayer requests
today underneath this video, Lord. And
can we ask you to just do something
amazing today and draw many by your
spirit and heal and provide and protect
and bless and encourage.
You're such a good God.
We're so undeserving of you. Thank you.
One day soon, Jesus, we will be face to
face with you. We will fall at your
feet.
Tears will be shed. Hugs will be given.
And we will worship the King of Kings
and the Lord of Lords forever and ever
without end. What a day that will be,
Lord.
We love you so much and we thank you and
we say all these things in your precious
name, Jesus. Amen. Okay, my friends.
So now
I am going to head off to church
and I'm going to start doing something
today because many people
out there ask me weekly, what church do
you go to? I'm a shut in. I don't have a
church, do they stream online? And yes,
they do. And what I think I'm going to
start doing today is
uh I'm going to head off to church now,
but I'm going to put I'm going to pin to
the top comment uh top of the comments.
I'm going to pin the scriptures I read
today and I'm also going to give you a a
link to uh Pastor Car's site, my pastor,
and he will do his service this morning.
and it will be live stream, but at 2:00
today, my time, New York City time, he
will have that uploaded to his channel
and I will pin I will then change the
pin comment and I will put the direct
link to the actual service that I'm
sitting in that maybe you want to be a
part of. That's all you know because I
know there's a lot of people that don't
have churches in their area that teach
truth. And uh Pastor Kerry is in the
middle of Galatians.
It's been an amazing study. So, I will
pin that. I will actually I will going
to set alarm every Sunday at 2:00 to pin
that direct link. So, if you check back
at 2, there will be a direct link in the
top comment of this video where you can
watch the same message that I'm going to
watch. Okay? And uh but again, before
then, I will put a link to his channel
to that playlist. So, if you wanted to
watch last week's or something to catch
up, that would be fine. But whatever, I
just felt led to do this and I hope it
blesses some out there who uh you know
before I found this church in this area.
There are there are a few good churches
and I found out about some of them after
I started attending the one I'm in now.
But before I attended Pastor Car's
church, it was hard for me to find a a
bibleelving church that had a pastor who
actually believed in the pre-tribulation
rapture. And so uh that's that. But
anyway, I'm going to head off there now
and I hope you guys have a a really
blessed day today. And uh you know, if
we're not raptured today, and I think
today is a perfectly good day for the
rapture, but if not today, God willing,
I will see you guys tomorrow. I love you
guys.
>> Oh [music] Jesus,
Savior,
master, [music]
creator.
[singing] You're the alpha.
Oh, [music]
you're the king of kings.